[
  {
    "question": "198+74",
    "answer": "272"
  },
  {
    "question": "15-6",
    "answer": "21"
  },
  {
    "question": "11+9",
    "answer": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "1+1",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "5*6",
    "answer": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "54+54",
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "29-23",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "69-8",
    "answer": "61"
  },
  {
    "question": "37-30",
    "answer": "67"
  },
  {
    "question": "20/5",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "54+54",
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "29-23",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "69-8",
    "answer": "61"
  },
  {
    "question": "37-30",
    "answer": "67"
  },
  {
    "question": "20/5",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "54+54",
    "answer": "108"
  },
  {
    "question": "29-23",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "69-8",
    "answer": "61"
  },
  {
    "question": "37-30",
    "answer": "67"
  },
  {
    "question": "20/5",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "126+8",
    "answer": "134"
  }
]